Marcelina Arabucka

Tel.: +357 96615424

Email: marcelina.a@gmail.com
Date of Birth: 24.03.1982
Marital Status: Single



Summary

My portfolio: www.marabucka.info.

I have been working commercially as a Graphic Designer (or DTP operator) for almost 5 years, including 3 years for one of Cyprus online-gaming companies where I gained experience as a web graphic designer in bingo/poker/casino industry.

I was responsible for designing marketing materials for new products and special offers: landing pages, icons, banners, mailers, newsletters etc. I re-designed some of company websites too. I am proficient in Adobe Photoshop and very good in whole Adobe Creative Suite (lately working with CS5).

As a DTP operator I was working day by day on creating newspaper's ads and marketing materials (leaflets, business cards, folders, catalogues etc.) and preparing them for printing. Additionally, I was delegated to work on layout and design for one of local weekly newspapers.

In my spare time I prepared layout and graphics for couple of other websites, including CyprusQA: www.cyprusqa.com

Skills

Technical Skills

- Graphics for web creating animated banners, icons, mailers, newsletters, landing pages.
- Web design (cutting and optimizing), basic HTML and CSS
- DTP (preparing files for printing, creating design and layout of catalogues, business cards, booklets, folders, calendars, logos, leaflets, etc.)

Software

- Proficient in: Adobe Photoshop, Corel Draw
- Good in: Adobe Flash, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Dreamweaver, QuarkXPress, Adobe InDesign
- Familiar with: 3d Studio Max, Adobe Premiere, Adobe After Effects, Xara3D

Experience

Graphic Designer, Limassol, Cyprus

June 2008 - December 2009 & July 2010-present*

* since August 2011 working from home, part time

CEC Management Ltd. (www.plexgaming.com, www.bingoentertainment.com)

- Primary responsibilities: designing banners, game images, mailers, newsletters, landing pages, flash animations, redesigning websites, creating logos, leaflets, headed papers
- Working in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Flash

Graphic Designer, Warsaw, Poland

February 2010 - June 2010

Poczta Kwiatowa (www.Pocztakwiatowa.pl)

- Primary responsibilities: designing banners, newspapers ads, catalogues of products, making photos of new products and flower arrangements.
- Working in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Flash

DTP Operator, Piaseczno /Warsaw

May 2007 - May 2008

Galia Advertisement & DTP (www.galia.net.pl)

- Primary responsibilities: designing advertisement materials and preparing it for printing; dealing with customers, creating design and layout of "Noonday Newsman".
- Working day by day in Corel Draw, QuarkXPress, Adobe Photoshop

Computer Graphic, Warsaw

February 2007 - May 2007

BEAM Laser Engrave

• Preparing (amending) Corel Draw files for laser's software

Junior Computer Graphic, Lodz (Internship)

May 2006 - September 2006

Transfer Multisort Elektronik (www.tme.pl)

- Working in marketing department on products catalogue
- Preparing products specifications (Corel Draw) and photos (correction and adjustments -Photoshop)

Education

Technical University of Lodz

October 2001- December 2006

- Master of Science, Computer Science (Computer Graphics and Multimedia)
- Master thesis: "Using 3d effects in television advertisements"
 (made using 3D Studio Max, Adobe Premiere, Adobe Photoshop, Corel Draw)

Additional Information

- Very good English, Basic Russian and Spanish, Polish is my mother tongue.
- Driving License.
- Interested in snorkeling, cinema, animal photography and traveling.